(Raj:)Now she knows I'm a desperate mess
instead of just being pretty sure!
(Raj:)It's Lucy.
(Raj:)She wants to meet for coffee.
I love you, Penny!
Hey, what are you working on?
(Sheldon:)I'm thinking about
how one could use the fact
(Sheldon:)that a rapidly rotating mirror
turns virtual photons into real ones
(Sheldon:)as a method of observing dark energy.
(Howard:)That's a pretty cool idea.
(Sheldon:)Yeah. It's great you're here.
(Sheldon:)I'd love to get
an engineer's opinion.
(Leonard:)Sure.
(Sheldon:)This chair is squeaky.
(Sheldon:)Now, do I fix it or get a new one?
(Leonard:)Well, Sheldon,
it took me all morning,
(Leonard:)but I found the owner
of the video store.
(Leonard:)And I am happy to report
that he died peacefully in his sleep,
(Leonard:)drunk at the bottom of a pool.
(Leonard:)Anyway, there is no one
to return the DVD to,